[
    {
    "language": "Spanish",
    "uuid": "b1303bf7-6575-41ea-93fb-4bb8da658eda",
    "progress": 0,
    "lessons": [
        {
        "subject": "Introduction to Spanish",
        "progress": 0,
        "intro": "Welcome to Big Sneeze's Spanish course! To start off we would like to say, Hola! That means \"Hello\" in Spanish!\nSome basic greetings are:\n",
        "keywords": [
            "Llamas : Name",
            "Hola : Hello",
            "Bienvindo : Welcome",
            "Amigo : Friend",
            "Gracias : Thanks",
            "Adios : Bye"
            ],
        "keyphrases": [
            "Por Favor : Please",
            "Buenas Noches : Good Night",
            "Buenas Tardes : Good Afternoon",
            "Buenos Dias : Good Morning",
            "Como te llamas? : What is your name?"
            ],
        "exercises": [
            {
            "question": "\"Hello\" in spanish is: _______",
            "type": "Fill_In",
            "options": "Hola  |  Como te llamas  |  Buenas dias  |  Buenas Noches",
            "answer": "Hola"
            },
            {
            "question": "Match the following to their spanish translation (format: \"1, 2, 3, 4\" english numbers) \nEnglish:\n1. Good night\n2. Hello\n3. Good morning\n4. What is your name\n",
            "type":"Matching",
            "options": "Spanish:\n1. Hola \n2. Como te llamas \n3. Buenas dias \n4. Buenas noches",
            "answer": "2, 4, 3, 1"
            },
            {
            "question": "Fill in the blank to say \"Good Morning\"\nBuenas ______",
            "type":"Fill_In",
            "options": "Llamas  |  Tardes  |  Dias  |  Noches",
            "answer": "Dias"
            },
            {
            "question": "Respond to the following: Beunas Dias!",
            "type":"Conversation",
            "options": "Llamas  |  Buanas Tardes  |  Buenas Dias  |  Buanas Noches",
            "answer": "Buenas Dias"
            },
            {
            "question": "Listen to the following audio and select an answer",
            "type":"Audio",
            "options": "Llamas  |  Tardes  |  Buenas Dias  |  Hola",
            "answer": "Hola"
            }
            ]
        },
        {
        "subject": "Common Spanish Phrases",
        "progress": 0,
        "intro": "In this lesson, we'll explore some commonly used Spanish phrases that will help you in daily conversations.",
        "keywords": [
            "Siento : Sorry",
            "Gracias : Thank you"
        ],
        "keyphrases": [
            "Lo siento : I'm sorry",
            "Gracias : Thank you",
            "Por favor : Please",
            "De nada : You're welcome"
        ],
        "exercises": [
            {
            "question": "\"I'm sorry\" in Spanish is: _________",
            "type":"Fill_In",
            "options": "Gracias  |  Lo siento  |  De nada  |  Por favor",
            "answer": "Lo siento"
            },
            {
            "question": "Match the following to their spanish translation (format: \"1, 2, 3, 4\" english numbers) \n English:\n1. Thank you\n2. Please\n3. Your welcome\n4. Im sorry\n ",
            "type":"Matching",
            "options": "Spanish:\n1. Por favor \n2. Gracias \n3. Lo siento \n4. De nada",
            "answer": "2, 1, 4, 3"
            },
            {
            "question": "Respond to someone saying \"Gracias\"",
            "type":"Conversation",
            "options": "Gracias  |  Por favor  |  De nada  |  Lo siento",
            "answer": "De nada"
            },
            {
            "question": "Listen to the following audio and select an answer",
            "type":"Audio",
            "options": "Gracias  |  Lo siento  |  De nada  |  Por favor",
            "answer": "Lo siento"
            },
            {
            "question": "What would you say if you accidentally stepped on someone's foot?",
            "type":"Matching",
            "options": "Gracias  |  Lo siento  |  De nada  |  Por favor",
            "answer": "Lo siento"
            }
        ]
        }
    ]
}
]
